Mss.Rec.29 Mss.Rec.29
American Philosophical Society
- Audio recordings
  - Red man's plaint about the white man's intrusion, 1959-07-20; 02-47; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:44; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Text given in Winnebago only, with an English introduction by the collector. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is the original tape's program 529.6.
  - About the Winnebago and Menominee, 1959-07-20; 02-48; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:28; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Text given in Winnebago only, with an English introduction by the collector. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is the original tape's program 529.7.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Menominee Indians; Winnebago Indians; Winnebago language--Texts
  - Forgiveness for a killer [4 of 4], 1959-07-20; 02-49; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:04; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Text given in Winnebago only, with an English introduction by the collector. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is the original tape's program 529.8.
  - Autobiographical story, 1959-07-20; 02-50; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:26; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Autobiographical story given in Winnebago only, with an English introduction by the collector. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is the original tape's program 529.9.
    Autobiography; Black River Falls (Wis.); Winnebago Indians
  - Ancillary eliciting, 1959-07-27; 02-51; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:50; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Winnebago language
  - Some exercises in transpositions and substitutions [2 of 2], 1959-07-22; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:23; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 19.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Winnebago language--Phonology; Winnebago language--Syntax
  - A story in Winnebago about a dream, with English translation, 1959-07-27; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:33; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Story given in Winnebago and then in English. English version begins at 3:02. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 19.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Dreams; Winnebago language--Texts
  - Ancillary eliciting to sentences from Swadesh word list, 1959-07-27; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:34; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Winnebago language; Winnebago language--Grammar
  - Ancillary eliciting to "A story about red-white rivalry and the background of an arrest", 1959-07-27; 03-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:09; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
  - Some statements made in "The Accentual System of Winnebago" by Amelia Susman rechecked, 1959-07-28; 03-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:17; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Text given in Winnebago only, with an English introduction by the collector. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 19.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Winnebago language--Grammar; Winnebago language--Verbs
  - The story explaining why a tell-tale is called a woodpecker in Winnebago, 1959-07-28; 03-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:26; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Story given in Winnebago only, with English introduction by the collector. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 19.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Talebearing; Winnebago Indians--Folklore; Winnebago language--Texts; Woodpeckers--Folklore
  - Translation of "The story explaining why a tell-tale is called a woodpecker in Winnebago", 1959-07-29; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:09:16; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 30.
  - About mourning of Indians, 1959-07-29; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:47; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Mourning customs--United States--Wisconsin; Winnebago Indians--Social life and customs
  - Ancillary eliciting, 1959-07-29; 04-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:30; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
  - Winnebago Sunrise Song, 1959-07-29; 04-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:53; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Sun--Rising and setting--Songs and music; Winnebago Indians--Music
  - The Lord's Prayer read by Mitchell Whiterabbit, 1959-07-29; 04-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:42; Fraenkel, Gerd; Whiterabbit, Mitchell
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Lord's Prayer; Winnebago language
  - Conversation between Alvin and Tilly Stacy, 1959-07-30; 04-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:24; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin; Stacy, Tilly
    Conversation in Winnebago. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 30.
    Greenwood (Wis.); Winnebago language
  - Winnebago pairs, 1959-07-30; 04-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:57; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
  - Explanation of Paul Radin's translations, 1959-07-31; 04-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:20; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Linguistic change; Radin, Paul, 1883-1959; Translating and interpreting; Winnebago language
  - The verbal system of Winnebago, 1959-07-17; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:11:16; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 17.
    Winnebago language--Verbs; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago minimal pairs, 1959-07-17; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:49; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Phonology; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago morphological forms taken from Hans Wolff's "Comparative Siouan", 1959-07-17; 05-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:36; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Morphology; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Story about a white man and an Indian, 1959-07-17; 05-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:35; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Story given in Winnebago and then in English. English version begins at 1:20. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 17.
    Winnebago Indians; Winnebago language--Texts; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Ancillary eliciting to "War of Indian tribes against white soldiers" [1 of 2], 1959-07-22; 05-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:11; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 547-end, 1959-07-29; 05-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:37:00; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 28.
    Greenwood (Wis.); Winnebago Indians--Religion; Winnebago Indians--Rites and ceremonies; Winnebago language--Texts; Winnebago mythology
  - Biography in Winnebago and English, 1959-07-14; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:33; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Recording contains a continuous, fluctuating background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from the original tape 14.
    Winnebago Indians--Rites and ceremonies; Winnebago language; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Swadesh 100-word list, 1959-07-14; 06-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:26; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from the original tape 14.
    Winnebago language; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago phrases and sentences containing words from the Swadesh 100-word list [1 of 2], 1959-07-14; 06-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:16:33; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 164-272, 1959-07-29; 06-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:09; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 25.
  - Winnebago phrases and sentences containing words from the Swadesh 100-word list [2 of 2], 1959-07-14; 07-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:01; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from the original tape 15.
  - Ancillary eliciting to sentences from Swadesh word list, 1959-07-14; 07-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:11:18; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language; Winnebago language--Grammar; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Word list from Hans Wolff's "Comparative Siouan", 1959-07-14; 07-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:14; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - Winnebago numbers, 1959-07-14; 07-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:09; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Glossaries, vocabularies, etc.; Winnebago language--Numerals; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago days of the week, 1959-07-14; 07-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:10; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Glossaries, vocabularies, etc.; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago decades, 1959-07-14; 07-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:38; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 273-417, 1959-07-29; 07-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:35:13; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 26.
  - Winnebago minimal pairs, 1959-07-17; 08-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:58; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 16.
  - Winnebago deictics, 1959-07-17; 08-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:27; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Deixis; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago possessives (paradigms and sentences), 1959-07-17; 08-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:57; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Possessives; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago comparative and superlative adjectives, 1959-07-17; 08-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:12; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Adjectives; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago names of places and peoples, 1959-07-17; 08-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:25; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - A pair of Winnebago words, 1959-07-17; 08-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:40; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - Winnebago prepositions, 1959-07-17; 08-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:52; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Winnebago language--Prepositions; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago expressions connected with colour, 1959-07-17; 08-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:44; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Colors, Words for; Winnebago language; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - Winnebago with/without expressions, 1959-07-17; 08-09; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:54; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
  - Winnebago expressions of time, 1959-07-17; 08-10; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:27; Fraenkel, Gerd; Smoke, Elias James
    Time--Terminology; Winnebago language; Wisconsin Dells (Wis.)
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 418-546, 1959-07-29; 08-11; 1.0 .mp3; 00:29:33; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 27.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version four, 1.4, 1959-07-30; 09-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:18:030; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 31.
  - The Journey of the Ghost to Spiritland: As Told in the Medicine Rite, 1-85, 1959-07-30; 09-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:17:08; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Culture of the Winnebago: As Described by Themselves," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 15, No. 1, Jan. 1949. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 31.
    Greenwood (Wis.); Reincarnation; Winnebago Indians--Religion; Winnebago Indians--Rites and ceremonies; Winnebago language--Texts; Winnebago mythology
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version one, 1-146, 1959-07-23; 09-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:32:07; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 20.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version four, 1.1-1.3 (middle), 1959-07-29; 10-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:37; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 29.
  - Ancillary eliciting to "War of Indian tribes against white soldiers" [2 of 2], 1959-07-22; 10-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:16:19; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 18.
  - Ancillary elicitng to "The red man's plaint against the white man about white supremacy", 1959-07-22; 10-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:21; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
  - A war story about a young girl, 1959-07-22; 10-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:42; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
    Story given in Winnebago and then in English. English version begins at 4:15. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program comes from original tape 18.
    Black River Falls (Wis.); Girls--Folklore; War--Folklore; Winnebago language--Texts
  - Some exercises in transpositions and substitutions [1 of 2], 1959-07-22; 10-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:39; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Stella
  - The Two Friends Who Became Reincarnated: The Origin of the Four Nights' Wake, 134-306, 1959-07-30; 11-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:34:12; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Culture of the Winnebago: As Described by Themselves," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 15, No. 1, Jan. 1949. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 32.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version one, 250-end, 1959-07-23; 11-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:45; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 22.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 1-40, 1959-07-23; 11-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:10:55; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
  - The Journey of the Ghost to Spiritland: As Told in the Medicine Rite, 86-102, 1959-07-30; 12-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:16; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Culture of the Winnebago: As Described by Themselves," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 15, No. 1, Jan. 1949. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 33.
  - The Two Friends Who Became Reincarnated: The Origin of the Four Nights' Wake, 1-125, 1959-07-30; 12-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:49; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version one, 147-249, 1959-07-23; 12-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:32:33; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 21.
  - The Two Friends Who Became Reincarnated: The Origin of the Four Nights' Wake, 307-463, 1959-07-30; 13-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:29:43; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Culture of the Winnebago: As Described by Themselves," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 15, No. 1, Jan. 1949. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 34.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version two, 41-163, 1959-07-23; 13-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:52; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 23.
  - The Two Friends Who Became Reincarnated: The Origin of the Four Nights' Wake, 464-528, 1959-07-31; 14-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:12; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Culture of the Winnebago: As Described by Themselves," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 15, No. 1, Jan. 1949. See Related Resource. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 35.
  - The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite, version three, 1-63, 1959-07-23; 14-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:16:24; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    A reading of a Winnebago text by a Winnebago speaker, with occasional corrections made. The text was transcribed by Paul Radin in "The Origin Myth of the Medicine Rite: Three Versions: The Historical Origins of the Medicine Rite," Supplement to the International Journal of American Linguistics, Vol. 16, No. 1, Jan. 1950. See Related Resource. Recording contains a continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 24.
  - Winnebago pairs, 1959-07-23; 14-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:26; Fraenkel, Gerd; Stacy, Alvin
    Recording contains a strong, continuous background hum. Copy made by Gerd Fraenkel of an original tape held at the Archives of Languages of the World, Indiana University. This program is from original tape 24.